Anyone can save the galaxy once.
Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 is a science fiction,
adventure, action film directed by James Gunn.
The Guardians must fight to keep their newfound family together as they
unravel the mysteries of Peter Quill's true parentage.
Peter Quill / Star-Lord, played by Chris Pratt.
Gamora, played by Zoe Saldaña.
Drax, played by Dave Bautista.
Baby Groot (voice), played by Vin Diesel.
Rocket (voice), played by Bradley Cooper.
Ego, played by Kurt Russell.
Guardians of the Galaxy Vol.
2: Awesome Mix Vol.
2 (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) is the soundtrack album for
the Marvel Studios film Guardians of the Galaxy Vol.
Featuring the songs present on Peter Quill's mixtape in the film, the
album was released by Hollywood Records on April 21, 2017.
A separate film score album, Guardians of the Galaxy Vol.
2 (Original Score), composed by Tyler Bates, was also
released by Hollywood Records on the same date.
Awesome Mix Vol.
2 was the United States' eighth best-selling album of 2017 with 600,000 copies.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic, sequel, misfit, space.
The tone is thought_provoking.